bzmr.com 2014-06-07

# Untitled Document

BZMR. PRIVACY POLICY

**Bzmr.com**

Slix Media, Inc. we appreciates our relationship with you, respects that your information is yours, and is committed to safeguarding your privacy when youre using our web site. The following describes our collection of and use of any information that we may collect from you.

**Questions**

If you have any questions, we can be reached via  
(contact at slixmedia at gmail dot com)

**Your Privacy at Bzmr.com**

We collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, we collect and store certain information automatically. Here is how we handle information about your visit to our website.

**What We Collect and Store Automatically**

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit: 

  * The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our website.
  * The type of browser and operating system used to access our site.
  * The date and time you access our site.
  * The pages you visit.
  * If you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website.
  * We use the information we collect to count the number and type of visitors to the different pages on our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors like you.

If you send us email, you may choose to provide us with personal information, as in e-mail with a comment or question. We use the information to improve our service to you or to respond to your request. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not share our e-mail with any other outside organizations.

**We do not use Cookies but our third party advertisers might use Cookies.**

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your computers hard drive through your web browser to enable us to recognize your computer and to deliver personalized features. The information collected by cookies is sometimes called â€œclickstreamâ€ or â€œclick trailâ€ and may also describe which areas of the Site you have used. We do not use cookies at this time. However, in the course of serving advertisements to this Site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. We do not receive any such information from our third party advertisers nor do we have any control over such third party advertisers or the use of any such information that is collected.

**We collect certain information if you request our Newsletter.**

We collect electronic mail information only if it is volunteered by you, such as your specific request to be added to our Newsletter mailing list. The information we collect from you if you subscribe to our Newsletter is used only to email the Newsletter to you.

**We may amend this Privacy Policy.**

If in the future this Privacy Policy is amended or updated, you will be subject to this Privacy Policy as amended or updated. We will not notify you of any amendments or updates to this Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy often for any changes hereto.

copyright 2011Bzmr. All Rights Reserved.
